<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" 
      xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" 
      xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" 
      xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" 
      version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>Lucas A. Meyer</title>
<link>https://www.meyerperin.com/index.html</link>
<atom:link href="https://www.meyerperin.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<description>Lucas A. Meyer's blog</description>
<generator>quarto-0.9.603</generator>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 07:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
  <title>Becoming Good at AI for Good</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-21-becoming-good-ai-for-good.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>The AI for Good Research Lab published an <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/publication/becoming-good-at-ai-for-good">article</a> last year about how to do AI projects in the #AI4Good domain.</p>
<p>The current training academia gives to data scientists is not very practical. People learn data science with very sanitized datasets in very idealized problems, and when they meet reality, it’s usually a big shock.</p>
<p>I think the “Becoming Good at AI for Good” article is a good summary regardless of whether you’re doing AI for Good or more “commercial” applications of AI. A lot of the problems that AI for Good projects face (and are addressed in the article) are also problems that you’ll see if you’re doing AI projects for organizations that don’t have software engineering as their primary capability.</p>
<p>I especially like the part about getting things from model to impact. Before learning of this article, I’d usually send people to an article that was written at Google in the early 2000s.</p>
<p>This is a lot better, and likely to help you understand a lot about the real-world constraints of making AI happen.</p>
<p>The article can be found at <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/publication/becoming-good-at-ai-for-good" class="uri">https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/research/publication/becoming-good-at-ai-for-good</a></p>



 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-21-becoming-good-ai-for-good.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/aiforgood.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Computers and Urinals</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-20-computer-urinal.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Years ago, in a tech conference, a researcher asked: “Isn’t it embarrassing that the conference center urinals can detect when you’re done and automatically flush, but your computer can’t detect that you’re not using it and automatically lock?”</p>
<center>
<img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/computer-urinal.jpg" class="img-fluid" style="width:40.0%">
</center>
<p>This seemingly simple problem is harder than it looks. People don’t (normally) quietly stare at urinals for several minutes, but that can happen to computer screens (e.g., watching a movie or presentation, reading a document).</p>
<p>Newer phones and tablets use eye tracking to save battery. They can figure out whether you’re looking at a screen, and if you’re not, lock. It works well, but these are devices that you almost always hold close to your face, so they can keep a camera pointing at you all the time. If you cover the camera or use an external monitor, you start having problems. With computers, I have a very strong preference for using external monitors, so I’m already in the problem situation to begin with. The solution could be to add a sensor to each monitor or camera, but given the <em>thousands</em> of models available, that could get complicated.</p>
<p>During my long career, I’ve seen many pranks on people that left their computers unlocked. Some places look down at the person who left the computer unlocked, but I actually prefer the places that chastise the pranksters: instead of pranking, it would be better if they locked the computer and kindly had a word with the forgetful person.</p>
<p>In any case, one of my favorite Windows 11 features (apparently also present in Windows 10) is the ability to lock my computer automatically when I move away from it.</p>
<p>The way to do that is a little convoluted: you need to pair your Bluetooth phone with your computer (which, of course, also needs to have Bluetooth), and when your computer, using Bluetooth, detects that your phone moved away from your computer, it will automatically lock.</p>
<p>From my description above, you probably already appreciate how a seemingly simple problem that we can solve for a urinal can be hard to solve even if your device has a lot more features.</p>
<p>The people who implemented the feature still couldn’t solve all problems. What to do if the user doesn’t have their phone today? Current solution: just show an error message. What to do if the user moves away but leaves the phone nearby? We detect phones, not users, so it will leave it unlocked.</p>
<p>In any case, I’m glad to see that computers of 2020s are inching closer to the toilets of the early 2000s.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-20-computer-urinal.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 22:10:22 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/computer-urinal.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Failing to lead by example</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-16-failing-to-lead-by-example.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>One of the worst things I have done as a manager was to go to a meeting. Luckily, I had a friend on that meeting (also a manager) that taught me something really important.</p>
<p>Here’s what I did wrong.</p>
<p>There was this meeting between several data science teams. It was really hard to find a time that worked for everybody. The meeting ended up being scheduled on a Friday morning, at about 9 AM on the day I was going on vacations. I couldn’t go, so I gave the meeting to one of my directs and we planned it out together. Some of the other teams had prep meetings, of which both me and my direct could (and did) participate. I couldn’t be on the big meeting to align on the roadmap, but it was well-supported and felt like everything was under control. Other members of my team would also attend to provide details about their projects, and they were well-prepared.</p>
<p>On the day of the meeting, which was also the first day of my long-awaited vacations, I was packed and ready to leave for my trip when I got a notice that my flight was delayed. I was planning to leave home a little after 9 AM, but now I could safely leave 10:30 AM and still arrive comfortably at the airport. Staying home longer would even mean less traffic to the airport.</p>
<p>With time to spare, I decided to join the meeting, even though I was a little late. When I joined, the meeting stopped, and people said something to the effect of “Oh, Lucas, I thought you were on vacation and were not going to join”, to which I responded: “I’m on vacations, but my flight was delayed. Since I could join and didn’t want to miss the meeting, I joined”.</p>
<p>Surprisingly directly and publicly, my friend on the meeting said: “Nah, you should log off. Otherwise, you’re going to start giving my team and your team the impression that they should join meetings during their vacations if they can, and that’s not setting a good example for work life balance”. (This was at Amazon, by the way).</p>
<p>I flushed for 10 seconds (it was an audio call only, thankfully) but realized she was completely right. I was a little embarrassed for being called out in public, but I’m usually not embarrassed for being wrong, at least not for long. I said: “You’re right, sorry for the disruption, I’m the least prepared for this meeting since I wasn’t planning to attend, and I’m sure I’ll be updated when I get back, I’ll drop off now”, got a bunch of “Have a good vacation” and disconnected.</p>
<p>In addition to showing that “vacations are important”, I also had the opportunity to show that “being wrong is ok”. Nobody was shutting me out. When I came back, I took over that workstream and ran it to the end. I was just making it harder for my team to help me by showing that I could help myself. Besides, we were just being fiercely protective of the work/life balance that we worked so hard to achieve on that group.</p>
<p>I didn’t realize the message I was sending, and I was glad to be called out.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-16-failing-to-lead-by-example.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/failing-to-lead.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Converting my blog from Jekyll to Quarto</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-10-jekyll-to-quarto.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>I thought moving from Jekyll to Quarto was going to be hard. It was not.</p>
<section id="what-i-wanted-in-a-blog-platform" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="what-i-wanted-in-a-blog-platform">What I wanted in a blog platform</h3>
<p>For a long time, I had an unfulfilled wish list for a blog platform:</p>
<ul>
<li>Can write posts in Markdown</li>
<li>Easy to deploy to Github</li>
<li>Can script in Python</li>
</ul>
<p>A large number of platforms fulfills the first two items, but I struggled to find one that fulfilled the last item. I finally found Pelican, but I found it too clunky and started to worry that it was not going to be maintained for long. Therefore, I oscillated between Jekyll and Hugo (using blogdown) for a long time. I liked blogdown a lot, but whenever I’m switching a lot between R and Python, my brain gets really unhappy.</p>
</section>
<section id="quarto-has-everything-and-more" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="quarto-has-everything-and-more">Quarto has everything, and more</h3>
<p>Recently, I found <a href="https://quarto.org">Quarto</a> that ticks all my boxes and solves a lot of other problems. My feeling when using Quarto must be similar to the feeling of Python programmers when they started using Jupyter (because they never used RStudio) or similar to what I felt when, as an analyst, started using RStudio. Things just work.</p>
<p>When I was initially switching between Jekyll and Hugo, one of the most annoying things was Jekyll preferred posts as files, while blogdown preferred posts as directories. RStudio even provides a function <code>bundle_site()</code> to convert files to directories. Now, when I’m converting to Quarto, I thought I needed to write such a function in Python.</p>
<p>Again, it turns out that “things just work”. Quarto accepts both directores and files as posts and rendered everything correctly. So I’m going to draw the “Quarto Spiral” instead, just to celebrate!</p>
</section>
<section id="example-from-hello-quarto" class="level3">
<h3 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="example-from-hello-quarto">Example from Hello, Quarto!</h3>
<div class="cell" data-execution_count="1">
<div class="sourceCode cell-code" id="cb1" style="background: #f1f3f5;"><pre class="sourceCode python code-with-copy"><code class="sourceCode python"><span id="cb1-1"><span class="im" style="color: #00769E;">import</span> numpy <span class="im" style="color: #00769E;">as</span> np</span>
<span id="cb1-2"><span class="im" style="color: #00769E;">import</span> matplotlib.pyplot <span class="im" style="color: #00769E;">as</span> plt</span>
<span id="cb1-3"></span>
<span id="cb1-4">r <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">=</span> np.arange(<span class="dv" style="color: #AD0000;">0</span>, <span class="dv" style="color: #AD0000;">2</span>, <span class="fl" style="color: #AD0000;">0.01</span>)</span>
<span id="cb1-5">theta <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">=</span> <span class="dv" style="color: #AD0000;">2</span> <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">*</span> np.pi <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">*</span> r</span>
<span id="cb1-6">fig, ax <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">=</span> plt.subplots(</span>
<span id="cb1-7">  subplot_kw <span class="op" style="color: #5E5E5E;">=</span> {<span class="st" style="color: #20794D;">'projection'</span>: <span class="st" style="color: #20794D;">'polar'</span>} </span>
<span id="cb1-8">)</span>
<span id="cb1-9">ax.plot(theta, r)</span>
<span id="cb1-10">ax.set_rticks([<span class="fl" style="color: #AD0000;">0.5</span>, <span class="dv" style="color: #AD0000;">1</span>, <span class="fl" style="color: #AD0000;">1.5</span>, <span class="dv" style="color: #AD0000;">2</span>])</span>
<span id="cb1-11">ax.grid(<span class="va" style="color: #111111;">True</span>)</span>
<span id="cb1-12">plt.show()</span></code></pre></div>
<div class="cell-output cell-output-display">
<div id="fig-polar" class="quarto-figure quarto-figure-center anchored">
<figure class="figure">
<p><img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-10-jekyll-to-quarto_files/figure-html/fig-polar-output-1.png" class="img-fluid figure-img"></p>
<p></p><p></p>
</figure>
</div>
</div>
</div>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-06-10-jekyll-to-quarto.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/quarto.png" medium="image" type="image/png" height="35" width="144"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Work life balance is worth something</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-05-10-work-life-balance.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Should you choose #Microsoft or #FAANG?</p>
<p>Last week, a Microsoft #recruiter I admire and has a lot of followers posted something about Microsoft being the gateway to FAANG. Having been into both Microsoft and FAANG and having participated on hundreds of recruiting processes for both (as an interviewer, hiring manager and interviewee), I have #feelings about this. Lots of feelings.</p>
<p>First off, let’s get my economist way of thinking and potential biases out of the way. By revealed preference, you know I prefer Microsoft to FAANG, at least under the conditions that were offered to me. I recently chose to come back to work for Microsoft from FAANG (I also had recent offers from other FAANGs). Therefore, take my words with a grain of salt.</p>
<p>Also, given recent performance, FAANGs are not an investment thing anymore. For pop-investing fans, the acronym is now MAMAA, one of which is Microsoft (Netflix was dropped).</p>
<p>But this doesn’t matter, since the main argument about FAANGs was about recruiting: FAANGs (allegedly) pay better than Microsoft. There are non-FAANG companies that also (at least used to) pay extremely well (e.g., Airbnb and Uber). When recruiters compete against FAANGs, it’s a difficult fight. It’s not uncommon to have a FAANG offer that is 50% over other companies. You don’t have to spend a lot of time in Blind to find out that in terms of total compensation, FAANGs pay very well.</p>
<p>I can tell you: it’s great to be paid very well. I can also tell you: it’s not the only thing that matters.</p>
<p>As a data scientist, I think a lot about optimization problems. If your personal career optimization problem is solving for maximizing short-term total compensation (TC), FAANGs are great. And, as that same recruiter wrote in a subsequent post, there’s no shame on having that goal.</p>
<p>But maybe you want to optimize for other things: work/life balance, impact, stress, learning, risk, work environment. Short-term TC is super important, especially in when you want to get a house, buy a car, get established, pay those student loans. But after some point, it may matter less to you. Privilege check: this is about choosing between high degrees of privilege, and I’m blessed and humbled to have the opportunity to choose, as many in the tech area do.</p>
<p>For the opportunities that were available to me, Microsoft was by far the best option for what I was optimizing for: learning, working with people I admire, work life balance, being able to talk about my work, having lasting impact on the world, and very good compensation with lower stock market risk.</p>
<p>As any person that knows about Goodhart’s Law or Charlie Munger can tell you, you get what you optimize for. When you’re choosing what you are optimizing for, make sure that it is what you really want.</p>



 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-05-10-work-life-balance.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/money-gun.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>How writing can help introverts communicate</title>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-24-writing-saves-introverts.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>I don’t like talking to people, but I don’t mind writing to them.</p>
<p>A little over a decade ago, during my MBA at #UWFoster, somebody I really admire told me: “you’re good at keeping in touch with the people you know”.</p>
<p>Truth is, I’m not that good at keeping in touch for many reasons, one of which being that I’m an extreme #introvert and initiating social interactions takes a lot of energy for me.</p>
<p>More recently, though, I found that #writing takes good care of that. Many people that I wanted to keep in touch with ended up getting in touch with me because of my writing here on #LinkedIn.</p>
<p>It works like MAGIC. It’s a lot easier for me to keep the conversations going after someone reaches out, and knowing what people I care about are currently doing honestly made my life better.</p>
<p>Of course, that works for me because I like writing, and even with three kids, I manage to find enough peace and quiet that I get to write from time to time. Some people find it better to “never have lunch alone”, or have a packed schedule of coffee meetings. Even as an introvert, I found that keeping in touch was important for me: I just needed to find a way that worked for me.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6924371471754571776" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6924371471754571776</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <category>neurodiversity</category>
  <category>writing</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-24-writing-saves-introverts.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/writing.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Joining Microsoft</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-18-joining-microsoft.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>I’m extremely happy to share that I’m starting a new position as Principal Data Scientist at the AI for Good Research Lab at Microsoft!</p>
<p><img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/just-hired-microsoft.jpg" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>This is an amazing team led by Juan M. Lavista Ferres, and I frequently still pinch myself to make sure it’s not just a dream, but instead, that it’s a dream come true.</p>
<p>My family is also super happy: my kids and even my mom wore #Microsoft shirts the whole weekend in support.</p>
<p>I bring the mug pictured below that I got two decades (!) ago when I first joined Microsoft in 2002. I will also bring all that I learned as a student and mentor at the University of Washington - Michael G. Foster School of Business.</p>
<p>I also want to thank Katie Baird, PCC for her incredible support in helping me find clarity in my career, and Jennifer Fink for introducing me to Katie.</p>
<p>Finally, I want to thank <em>you</em>, yes, you, who interacted with me and the content I put out here on LinkedIn.</p>
<p>I learn a lot from #writing, and from interacting with you. Thanks for making writing worthwhile, and I hope my content is helpful to you in some way.</p>
<p>It’s an exciting and energizing new beginning, and there’s a lot of people and organizations to empower to achieve more.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6921815848412135424" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6921815848412135424</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-18-joining-microsoft.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/just-hired-microsoft.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Bear on tree</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-17-bear-on-tree.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>During a couple of our conference calls, I told my team that I needed a moment because I needed to deal with a bear situation. Usually it was quick, just the dog barking a lot, or an overturned trash can. I’m not sure they believed me.</p>
<p>Today I was able to get good pictures of a young black bear that climbed a tree some 30 feet behind my backyard.</p>
<p>It’s truly special to live so close to nature and I really hope we’re not bothering the bears too much.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lucasameyer_during-a-couple-of-our-conference-calls-activity-6921261803536560128-JJ1z" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lucasameyer_during-a-couple-of-our-conference-calls-activity-6921261803536560128-JJ1z</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>home</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-17-bear-on-tree.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/bear-tree-2.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Farewell Lunch</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-15-farewell-lunch.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>It was a good farewell lunch at #Amazon. It was a nice day (for #Seattle standards) and the company was top notch. My team at Amazon was very distributed, with some people in San Diego, some people in Vancouver and some in Seattle, so the sad part is that I only got to see the Seattle team.</p>
<p>On the upside, we finally got to know how tall everyone really is, although I think some people were wearing heels. 😀</p>
<p>Thanks Tali Behar for the game and for the restaurant tips, Nisma Nayyar for the delicious baklavas, Haiying Zheng for coming even in your off-time, and Mina Loghavi for all your #leadership and guidance. Thanks to Mark Manning for taking the picture and for being always awesome.</p>
<p>MJ Brooks, MMR , Amrut Deshpande , Joyce Guo, Yuexiu (Rachel) Jin , Amol Palekar , Jiating Lin , Aravind Kumar , Yudi Z. Erin (Xinying) Li, Yuanyong (Esmeralda) Chen, Siddharth Gupta, Raghu Vamsy Sirasala, yuling xiong: you’ve been a wonderful team and I’m sorry we didn’t get to meet in person. I hope we’ll get together sometime.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lucasameyer_amazon-seattle-leadership-activity-6920874431531618304-nxUL" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/posts/lucasameyer_amazon-seattle-leadership-activity-6920874431531618304-nxUL</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-15-farewell-lunch.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/farewell-lunch.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>My policies on interviewing</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-13-my-policies-around-interviewing.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>I have recently announced that I’m leaving Amazon and starting a new job (yet to be announced) next week. This means that I have been on the interviewee side of the interview process somewhat recently.</p>
<p>One of the most important things to know is that the way of getting better at interviewing is… well, interviewing! It’s good to be on both sides of the table, both as an interviewer and as an interviewee. Practice helps you to do better, but it also helps you see where you’re not doing well.</p>
<p>I have two policies about interviewing. The first policy is that I will accept an invitation to interview at least once a year, even if I’m happy with my job, which I frequently am. I don’t like wasting people’s time, so it has to be a place that I would really consider going to if the process worked out. The reason for that policy is that I once spent many years without interviewing and when a good opportunity showed up, I was very out of practice, and I think a lot of me not getting it was because I barely understood how the process worked in other companies. I’m not sure I’ll keep this policy.</p>
<p>The second policy, which I’m even less sure of its helpfulness, is that once I decide that I’m willing to change jobs, I will be fairly open to interview for lots of different things. For example, if I get invited to interview for my dream job and decide that I would leave my current job for it, I’ll interview for lots of other jobs as well. This gives me a lot of extra work and stress (interviewing is hard), but it also allows me to practice a lot and find my weaker spots, and to have a backup in case things don’t work out.</p>
<p>One of the hardest questions for me is “why do you want to leave your current job and join us”. I tend to like the job I have, and also tend to be more forthcoming than the average interviewee. My sincere answer is usually far away from “this is my dream job”. It’s possible that I have only succeeded in my latest interview because it’s a place that I really, really, really love and admire in a company that I love and admire, too. It was sincerely my dream job and team. In any case, after some practice in interviews (and lots of help from Katie Baird, PCC) I started to get better at answering that question, while still being sincere, which led to far more offers/quasi-offers.</p>
<p>To wrap this up, I want to recognize that my experience above is one of extreme privilege: I have been around for a long time, and I’m extremely fortunate to be invited to interview. A large number of people are in earlier stages, when even getting an interview is hard. If you are in that situation, I think the takeaway is to still try to get as much practice as you can (by being open even after you’re far into some process, by doing mock interviews in both sides of the table, etc.). I hope your time will come and I hope that I can help.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6919995369711906816" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6919995369711906816</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <category>hiring</category>
  <category>interviewing</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-13-my-policies-around-interviewing.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/offer-only.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Leaving Amazon</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-11-leaving-amazon.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>This is my last week at Amazon. I will announce my new position (which is beyond awesome) early next week.</p>
<p>The time I spent at Amazon was great: I have learned an incredible amount and my career grew substantially. Recruiting was superb, training was excellent, and work-life balance (at least on my team) was extremely good. If you have the opportunity to work for Amazon, it’s a solid choice. In particular, CTPS is a great team to work for. The leadership on my team was inspiring: not only they are smart and accomplished, they are also great human beings. I will miss them.</p>
<p>What I will miss the most, however, are the people in my immediate team, many of whom I hired myself. I will miss you a lot. You are extremely competent and I’m lucky to have worked with you for this period of time, which now feels way too short. I learned a lot from you and will take it with me in my future adventures. I wish you the very best on your careers and I hope we meet again soon.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6919333255288627200" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6919333255288627200</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <category>hiring</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-11-leaving-amazon.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 11 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/mac-power-off.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Hiring is a superpower</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-05-hiring-is-a-superpower.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>One of my superpowers from my #Amazon review process this year was “Hire and Develop the Best”.</p>
<p>This may be because a few years ago, my (then) manager taught me a trick: when in doubt, err on the side of hiring people.</p>
<p>I looked at my statistics a while back and I really don’t say “yes” that much more than my peers. It’s just a little more. When I shadowed other interviewers, I noticed that my questions are just as hard, if not harder. If I noticed one difference, it’s that I tend to start with a quick, easier question, which usually cost me less than five minutes, and I’m then quickly at or above the average difficulty level of my peer interviewers.</p>
<p>I do this because it is extremely common for the interviewee to be nervous during an interview. Like on the movie Gladiator, you don’t know what will come out when the gates open, even though you prepared a lot for it. If the first question throws the interviewee off, it’s often hard for them to regain confidence. It’s quicksand.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/gladiator.jpg" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>I like #interview questions that are “adaptive”, like the GMAT, meaning that you can make them easier or harder by changing small things. Sometimes, people would actually be able to do the hard version of the question, but they’re nervous and need to start with the easy one.</p>
<p>As commonplace as it is, the interview process is very imperfect, and usually tends to yield false negatives: meaning that it fails people that would have succeeded. Given how hard the process is, people that are “on the margin” are more likely to be good hires than not. I have not regretted any bets I’ve made.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6917105322906005506" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6917105322906005506</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>career</category>
  <category>hiring</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-05-hiring-is-a-superpower.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/gladiator.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>South Carolina dolphins!</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-04-south-carolina-dolphins.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>After a long winter in Seattle, I finally got some vacations, which I used to visit the Isle of Palms, SC.</p>
<p>One of the days, since the weather was great, but under heavy protests of the teenagers, we went to a beach that was mostly empty.</p>
<p>“But daaaaaad, there will be nothing to dooooo but look at the seeeeea”.</p>
<p>So we looked at the sea, jumped waves, built a tiny sand castle. Then I caught something at the corner of my eye.</p>
<p>“Provably just a bird, dad.”</p>
<p>I didn’t think it was a bird - so I kept looking at the sea. A few moments later… a fin comes out of the water. A shark? No, it was a dolphin.</p>
<p>Now everybody was looking at the sea, checking out the dolphins in the wild.</p>
<p>After that, the day became “the day we saw the dolphins”.</p>
<p>I hope that your spring break is as enjoyable as mine.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6916579598633701376" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6916579598633701376</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-04-south-carolina-dolphins.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/lucas-in-charleston.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Chesterton’s Fence</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-02-chestertons-fence.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Chesterton’s Fence is an extremely important concept, especially if you are joining a new team in a senior or in a leadership position.</p>
<p>The concept dates from around 1929. The original text is longer, but a concise version is: “Do not take a fence down if you don’t know why it was put up in the first place.”</p>
<p>New managers and senior resources frequently want to change a lot of things. We are, after all, hired because of our deep expertise and experience. It’s not uncommon for a senior, experienced person to think that what was done before them was “wrong” and that they could easily do what’s “right”.</p>
<p>The reality is that, most times, whomever did the previous version is an accomplished professional had to make lots of decisions under constrained resources. I find that it’s usually hubris from my side to think that I can easily understand and solve all those problems quicker and better than they did. Fences don’t sprout from the ground - there’s a reason why a specific fence was put up there in the first place.</p>
<p>I frequently learn a lot when trying to understand the reasons why the original decisions were made. Occasionally, the original solution can really be improved on, but after understanding why it was made in the first place I also learn of constraints I didn’t know. In many other cases, I learn of constraints that would actually create significant problems for the new idea I had, and that saves me and everyone else significant time.</p>
<p>When I was less experienced and less careful, I brought down plenty of fences unnecessarily, and was later surprised to find escaped sheep on the road and farmers yelling at me</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/embed/feed/update/urn:li:share:6915688739935522816" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/embed/feed/update/urn:li:share:6915688739935522816</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>concepts</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2022-04-02-chestertons-fence.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/fence.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Using corn cob lights to beat seasonal blues</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-12-14-using-corn-cob-lights-to-beat-seasonal-blues.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>There are a lot of tech companies in Seattle, always hiring (I will myself post a new position soon). And if you know something about Seattle, it’s probably that it rains a lot.</p>
<p>For all its fame, #Seattle gets 37 inches of rain per year. Sunny Miami gets 62 inches. Of course, measuring things is tricky, and an art that we #DataScientists are (or at least should be) very familiar with. Measuring things differently, Seattle has around 150 “sunny days” per year, and Miami has around 250. That’s almost three months less.</p>
<p>Measuring things in yet another way, the average number of hours of sunlight in Seattle per year is approximately 2,000. Miami and LA get approximately 3,200. Las Vegas gets 3,800. Besides being cloudy and rainy, Seattle is further to the north, and the sun sets before 5 PM for a large part of the winter.</p>
<p>I find that the lack of sunlight gets to me a lot more than the rain and the temperature, both of which I actually enjoy.</p>
<p>One trick I learned is to use “corn cob lightbulbs” everywhere in my house. A 50W corn cob bulb produces 5,000 lumens. A typical 13W CFL light produces about 1,000 lumens, the same as a 60W incandescent light. After installing corn cob lightbulbs in my office, I started feeling a lot less tired after a long day of #wfh during the winter, even finding energy to cook and play board games with my kids.</p>
<p>If you’re considering to move to Seattle, it’s not about the umbrellas. It rarely rains hard enough to justify using one. It’s more about finding a way of being outside when there’s sunlight (and there are plenty of great things to do around Seattle what that’s the case) and getting enough illumination when one can’t go out.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6887089031746854912" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6887089031746854912</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-12-14-using-corn-cob-lights-to-beat-seasonal-blues.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/rainy-day.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Weak baselines</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-29-weak-baselines.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Gather close as I tell you another cautionary tale about data science.</p>
<p>The finance team of a company was trying to forecast their monthly cash. An analyst had been doing that for about ten years, and had a record of cash actually received per month going back all those years. He realized that some months, like December, received a lot more cash than others, like February.</p>
<p>The analyst used Excel to calculate the percentage change for each month. For example, if the company received $100M in October 2009 and $80M in November 2009, he recorded -20% for Nov 2009. To calculate November 2021, he would take the average of the percentage changes for November over the last 10 years (2011 to 2020) and apply it to the October 2020 number.</p>
<p>It didn’t work too well. The mean absolute percentage error (MAPE) was around 20%. For some months, the forecast missed by a lot, causing significant problems, including having to urgently borrow cash at significant cost. Eventually, the company decided to hire a data science consulting company.</p>
<p>The consulting company immediately concluded that the problem was due to lack of data. Ten years of monthly data resulted in just 120 data points. To do data science, they said, they needed more than that. Luckily, the analyst had also been recording the daily data. Now, with thousands of data points, the consulting company used an LSTM deep learning model to forecast cash by day. It also didn’t work too well, but when they aggregated it by month, it did a lot better than the analyst’s original forecast: MAPE was closer to 10%.</p>
<p>The project was celebrated as a success. A press release was issued, promoting the benefits of using cloud technologies and deep learning for more accurate financial forecasting. The person who hired the consultants was promoted.</p>
<p>A few months later, a new data scientist joined the company, looked at the monthly data, and used the Excel FORECAST.ETS function to achieve a MAPE of 1% in seconds. This time, there was no press release.</p>
<p>When starting a data science project, be careful about the baseline you’re using to determine success. Choosing a poor baseline (like the original analyst model) can result in thinking that fairly bad outcomes (like the one from the LSTM model) are good, just because they’re better than horrible outcomes. I’ve seen a number of cases in which a simple heuristic handily beat a complicated ML model.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to Linkedin at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6871097167612915712" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6871097167612915712</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>data science</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-29-weak-baselines.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/weak-baseline.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reverse causation</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-22-reverse-causation.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Gather close as I tell you a cautionary tale about data science.</p>
<p>A new data scientist had just started working on the collections team for a large company. One of the problems they wanted to solve was “does contacting customers help at all?”</p>
<p>It’s an important question. After all, the cost of collections is directly related to the number of contacts. The more contacts, the more people.</p>
<p>The DS had a table with of invoices and payment dates, and a table with a history of contacts by invoice. Using the invoice issue date and invoice payment date, he created a payment delay metric. Then, he joined the contact history and created a metric for number of contacts. Finally, he calculated the correlation between the number of contacts and payment delay.</p>
<p>He was startled by the results: the more contacts per invoice, the <em>longer</em> it took customers to pay.</p>
<p>He told the collections manager, who got very excited. He long suspected that the contact center had too many people. Now he had some proof.</p>
<p>The DS carefully separated the data in a training and a test sample, and trained a regression model using XGBoost. Given inputs such as the invoice country and amount, the model predicted the delay in days given an estimated number of contacts. The model had a very low error (&lt;0.5d) in the training dataset. When using the unseen test dataset, the error was also minimal.</p>
<p>The DS and the collections manager made a plan to deploy a tool to collectors. When assigned an invoice, collectors should enter the characteristics of the invoice in the tool and add 1 contact. For example, if a collector was assigned an invoice with 10 days delay and 2 contacts, they should enter 3 as the number of contacts. If the model returned a number larger than the current delay, the collector should not make the contact. They should just wait.</p>
<p>Once the tool was deployed, the number of contacts initially dropped a lot. To the collections manager surprise, however, the payment delays also increased. Customers were paying much later than usual, and ended up having to be contacted anyway.</p>
<p>As you may already have realized, the problem with the idea was that customers were not delaying because they were annoyed with too many contacts. The relation went in the other direction: customers were being contacted because they were late. While contacts and lateness was very correlated, lateness caused contacts, not the other way around.</p>
<p>The project was scrapped. The team decided that data science was all hype. The data scientist moved on to another team. The collections team went back to the old way of contacting customers: about once per week until they paid.</p>
<p>It took a while (and a new data scientist) for that team to trust data science again: a few years later, a new data scientist started experimenting with assigning different strategies to randomized customers, and that improved collections a lot. But that’s another tale.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6868560453447118848" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6868560453447118848</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>data science</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-22-reverse-causation.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/reverse-causation.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Cunningham’s Law</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-04-cunninghams-law.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Cunningham’s Law states “the best way to get the right answer on the internet is not to ask a question; it’s to post the wrong answer.”</p>
<p>It’s not only applicable to the internet. I find that it works in a lot of other interactions, including work interactions.</p>
<p>Cunningham’s Law is frequently presented as a way to exploit a bias that people potentially have against “things being wrong”. While the “bias exploitation” story may be true, there’s also an economic reason why using Cunningham’s Law is a nice thing to do.</p>
<p>A common example of when posting the wrong answer is expected is in Stack Overflow: when asking your question, it’s a good practice to show what you already tried and what’s not working (essentially posting the wrong answer).</p>
<p>The advantage of such a protocol is that it makes it easier on the people trying to help. Consider the example “Who is Luke’s father?”. Asked as a question, there’s a lot of context missing: Luke the Apostle? Luke Skywalker? Luke Wilson? My neighbor Luke?</p>
<p>On the other hand, the incorrect statement “Han Solo is Luke’s father” provides a lot of additional context: this is about Star Wars, and it also provides how the question asker expects the answer to look like. Economically, it lowers the production cost of an answer, making it easier to get one.</p>
<p>… and if there’s something wrong with my theory above, I’m sure someone is going to correct me!</p>
<p><img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/cunninghams-law.jpg" class="img-fluid"></p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6862028173295648769" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6862028173295648769</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>concepts</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-11-04-cunninghams-law.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/cunninghams-law.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Reverse laziness</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-10-27-reverse-laziness.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>I’ve noticed a behavior in both my professional life and with my kids doing their homework: people spend a lot of time on things they don’t like.</p>
<p>Many years ago, I had that realization about myself. For some things I didn’t like doing, I’d procrastinate, complain, but ultimately ended up having to be engaged with that task over a long period of time. During that time, the stress of the task kept hanging over me.</p>
<p>I decided to do a deal with myself: I’d set up a short but reasonable time to do the task and during that time I’d do the best I could. At the end, I’d be <em>done</em>. Back then, I didn’t know about the #pomodoro method, which can actually be used in a similar way.</p>
<p>After that, the “dwell time” of tasks that annoyed me dropped sharply: once I booked the time, the task was mostly out of my mind. Once I finished the allocated time, I’d be in peace. Things that used to annoy me for a week became things that bothered me for an hour.</p>
<p>I even started to like some of the tasks I thought I wouldn’t. Getting started is half the battle.</p>
<p>I still couldn’t convince my kids.</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at:<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6859131315925721088" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6859131315925721088</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>concepts</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-10-27-reverse-laziness.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/reverse-laziness.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
<item>
  <title>Do you know how smart I am in Portuguese?</title>
  <dc:creator>Lucas A. Meyer</dc:creator>
  <link>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-10-10-do-you-know-how-smart-i-am-in-portuguese.html</link>
  <description><![CDATA[ 



<p>Recently, several people at work said they liked my #writing.</p>
<p><img src="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/smart-portuguese.jpg" class="img-fluid"></p>
<p>English is not my native language. It’s Portuguese. I was actually a pretty good writer in Portuguese: I won a few writing contests, and got high writing grades in standardized tests.</p>
<p>I moved to the US when I was almost 30, and as much as I had studied English in high school and self-studied it quite a lot more, moving countries was hard. For example, most of the rote phrases that people say in daily interactions such as “how’s your weekend going?” were literally foreign to me. It took me a while to realize that nobody really wanted to know about my weekend.</p>
<p>Quite a bit of academics later, I started writing, mostly for myself. I found, to nobody’s surprise, that writing makes one’s thoughts clearer. About a year ago, I joined #Amazon. At Amazon, we literally write for a living. A number of work processes require writing documents. I also started to write to a broader audience here on LinkedIn, and I get the occasional (and very much appreciated) note from people that tell me that they like my writing and that it helped them.</p>
<p>I still don’t meet my own ever-rising bar, and I still throw away a lot of what I write. But writing has helped me gain clarity, and I hope it helps others, too!</p>
<section id="linkedin" class="level4">
<h4 class="anchored" data-anchor-id="linkedin">LinkedIn</h4>
<p>This was posted to LinkedIn at <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6853333112810815488" class="uri">https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:share:6853333112810815488</a></p>


</section>

 ]]></description>
  <category>writing</category>
  <guid>https://www.meyerperin.com/posts/2021-10-10-do-you-know-how-smart-i-am-in-portuguese.html</guid>
  <pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
  <media:content url="https://www.meyerperin.com/images/smart-portuguese.jpg" medium="image" type="image/jpeg"/>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
